<LinearLayout xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:layout_margin="20dp"
    android:gravity="center"
    android:orientation="vertical">

    <ScrollView
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content">
        <TextView
            android:id="@+id/terms_conditions"
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="740dp"
            android:layout_marginLeft="20dp"
            android:layout_marginRight="20dp"
            android:layout_marginBottom="100dp"
            android:gravity="center"
            android:scrollbars="vertical"
            android:textColor="@color/gen_black"
            android:text="The terms and conditions published here in is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules there under as applicable and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000.
This electronic record is generated by a computer system and does not require any physical or digital signatures.
\nThe terms and conditions published herein in accordance with the provisions of Rule 3 (1) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries guidelines) Rules, 2011 that require publishing the rules and regulations, privacy policy and Terms and Conditions for access or usage of www.SportEase.in Application.
\n \nThe domain name www.sportease.in and the mobile application SportEase Online Shopping App (hereinafter collectively referred to as Application) is owned by sportease Sports India Pvt. Ltd. (hereinafter referred to as SportEase) a company incorporated under the Companies Act, 1956 with its registered office at Survey No. 78/10 A20- Chikkajala Village, Bellary Road, (PO Box No. 1, Bettahalsoor Post Office) Bangalore - 562157, Karnataka, India.
For the purpose of these Terms and Conditions, wherever the context so requires Buyer shall mean any natural or legal person who has agreed to become a buyer on the Application by providing Registration Data while registering on the Application as Registered Buyer using the computer systems.
Decathlon allows the Buyer to surf the Application without registering on the Application,
however to make purchases, the Buyer must be registered on the Application.
For the purpose of the above, Registration Data shall include the following information which is entered by the User at the time of accessing and registering themselves on the Application: i) Name ii) Gender iii)Contact Number iv) Email ID v) Pincode
When The Buyers use any of the services provided by SportEase through the Application, including but not limited to, (e.g. Product Reviews), The Buyers will be subject to the rules, guidelines, policies, terms, and conditions applicable to such service, and they shall be deemed to be incorporated into this Terms and Conditions and shall be considered as part and parcel of this Terms and Conditions. Decathlon reserves the right, at Decathlon's sole discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of these Terms and Conditions, at any time without any prior written notice to The Buyers. It is Buyer's responsibility to review these Terms and Conditions periodically for updates / changes.
Buyer's continued use of the Application following the posting of changes will mean that The Buyers accept and agree to the revisions.
As long as The Buyers comply with these Terms and Conditions, SportEase grant The Buyers a personal, non-exclusive, non-transferable, limited privilege to enter and use the Application.
\n\nACCESSING, BROWSING OR OTHERWISE USING THE SITE INDICATES BUYER'S AGREEMENT TO ALL THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS, SO PLEASE READ THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY BEFORE PROCEEDING.. By impliedly or expressly accepting these Terms and Conditions, the Buyers also accept and agree to be bound by SportEase Policies (including but not limited to Privacy Policy, Terms of Service (TOS) etc.) as amended from time to time.
\n\nUse of the Application is offered to the Buyer conditioned on acceptance without modification of all the terms, conditions and notices contained in this Agreement and TOS, as may be posted on the Application from time to time. For the removal of doubts, it is clarified that use, accessing, browsing or otherwise using of the Application by the User constitutes an acknowledgement and acceptance by the User of this Agreement, TOS and Privacy Policy.
\n\nIf the Buyers are a minor i.e. under the age of 18 years, the Buyers shall not register as a buyer of the SportEase Application and shall not transact on or use the Application. As a minor if the Buyers wish to use or transact on the Application, such use or transaction may be made by Buyer's legal guardian or parents on the Application. SportEase reserves the right to terminate Buyer's membership and / or refuse to provide the Buyers with access to the Application if it is brought to Decathlon's notice or if it is discovered that the Buyers are under the age of 18 years."
            android:justificationMode="inter_word"
            android:textSize="16sp" />
    </ScrollView>
</LinearLayout>
